{
    "subject": "resource/Mutterschied",
    "predicate": "ontology/associationOfLocalGovernment",
    "object": "resource/Simmern",
    "human_readable": "Mutterschied is associated with Simmern.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9864538311958313,
            "question": "Describe the association between Mutterschied and Simmern."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9739123582839966,
            "question": "Is there a relationship between Mutterschied and Simmern?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.943821370601654,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Mutterschied and Simmern?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9365898370742798,
            "question": "How are Mutterschied and Simmern related?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.914648175239563,
            "question": "What is known about the connection between Mutterschied and Simmern?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9133864641189575,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the link between Mutterschied and Simmern?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6750695109367371,
            "question": "Name the location linked to Simmern."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5840521454811096,
            "question": "What town is associated with Simmern?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5550829172134399,
            "question": "Which place is connected to Mutterschied?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4113946259021759,
            "question": "What town has a connection with Simmern?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mutterschied is associated with Simmern.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5546_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which place is connected to Mutterschied?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5546_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What town is associated with Simmern?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5546_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the location linked to Simmern.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5546_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5546_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5546_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5546_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5546_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5546_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5546_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5546_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5546_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5546_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5546_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about routes between Mutterschied and Simmern/Hunsr\u00fcck, indicating that these two locations are indeed associated. ViaMichelin offers travel guidance and options for journeys between the two places, which supports the association."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}